



8884577846



haleshab1995@gmail.com



11-May-1995



https://www.linkedin.com/in/haleshabandri/



1250, 6th ward, Near Banashankari Temple, Kottur-583134, Vijayanagar(dist.), Karnataka, India

HALESHA BANDRI

SUMMARY

Senior Qlik Developer with over 8+ years of comprehensive experience in the field of data analytics and my professional journey has spanned diverse sectors in manufacturing and pharma and expertized majorly in Qlik sense, Redshift SQL, S3, Data Modelling, QMC, Qlik N-Printing, Viz-lib extensions.

EDUCATION

| COURSE | NAME OF INSTITUTION | BOARD | Per(%) | YEAR |
|--------|--|--------|-----------|---------------------|
| B.E. | Sri Siddhartha Institute Of Technology, Tumkur | Deemed | 9.2(CGPA) | Aug 2012 - May 2016 |
| II PUC | SGT Swamy PU College, Kottur | DPUE | 80.50% | Jun 2010 - May 2012 |
| SSLC | Sri Kolashantheshwara High School, Kottur | KSEEB | 83.04% | Jun 2007 - May 2010 |

WORK HISTORY

Senior Qlik Sense Developer

Company: Accenture | Team: Market op's | Client: Astellas Pharma | Period: Jan 2023-Present Date

- Developed dashboards like email marketing analysis (Campaign emails and Rep triggered emails),
 Medical rep call analysis and adobe web analytics which will help to analyse the performance of
 multiple digital marketing and provide optimized recommendations for 10+ brands across 15+
 countries.
- Migrated Power BI apps to Qlik sense enterprise environment.
- Working with front end technologies like HTML, CSS, Java Script, Bootstrap for creation of Mashup's.
- Optimized Global Data model and worked closely with Data engineering team in order to meet customer requirements.
- Integrated Viz-lib extensions to Qlik Sense and utilized them for additional functionality.
- Utilized Qlik N-Printing to automate report generation and distribution.
- Tested and monitored dashboard test cases using ALM testing tool.
- Leveraged Agile methodology with Azure DevOps to streamline project planning, tracking, and team collaboration
- Scheduled and automated dashboard refreshes using Control-M tool.
- **Skill's:** Qlik Sense (Nov-2024), QMC, AWS Redshift (DWH), S3(DL), Redshift SQL, Viz-lib extensions, Azure Dev Ops (Agile), HP **ALM** Tool, control-M, Power BI, HTML, CSS, Java script.

Qlik Sense Developer

Company: TCS | Team: OBD Team | Client: CNC & Ozone Pharmaceuticals | Period: Mar 2019-Dec 2022

- Developed dashboards like Sales analysis, procurement analysis, collection analysis, outstanding analysis for manufacturing clients.
- Handled end to end Complete Software Development Life Cycle (SDLC) of dashboards.
- Involved in analysing the Business Requirement Document (BRD) and defined Key Performance Indicators (KPI's).
- Implemented Incremental Data Load process for Load Optimization.
- Experience in writing complex and Efficient SQL Queries.
- Well versed with Qlik Sense Scripting and Set Analysis.
- Implemented Data Security using Section access.
- Optimized Qlik scripts in the backend as well as in the front end.
- Scheduled jobs for QVD extracts and report reloads.
- Skills: Qlik Sense (May-2022), QMC, MySQL (DWH), Postman.

SQL Developer

Company: TCS | Team: Out Bound Reports | Project: TCS ion ERP Solution | Period: Feb 2017 - Mar 2019

- Gathered requirements from manufacturing customer and analysed the requirements and developed customized reports using **Pentaho** report designer and **MYSQL Database**.
- Experience in designing the database tables, views, indexes and writing Stored Procedure, Functions and Triggers.
- Experience in MYSQL Query design, writing complex queries.
- Experience in implementing Normalization Techniques and Datawarehouse concepts.
- Handled OLTP and OLAP databases and Data modelling techniques.
- Proficient in troubleshooting MYSQL queries and fixing the Query defects by validating SQL code.
- Handled Performance tuning and Query optimization techniques on MYSQL Queries by re-writing queries, by applying proper indexing on columns and by analysing Query EXPLAIN PLANS.
- Ability to work in Agile environment.
- Skills: MySQL, Pentaho, Jenkins, XML.

SKILLS

| Languages | SQL, LINUX, HTML, CSS, JS |
|-------------|---------------------------------------|
| BI Tools | Qlik Sense, Power BI, Pentaho |
| ETL Tools | Informatica |
| Databases | MYSQL, Oracle, Redshift SQL |
| Other Tools | Jenkins, Excel, Tortoise SVN, Postman |

ACCOMPLISHMENTS

- Received appreciation mails from Clients for on time completion and meeting client requirements.
- Received gems as a token of appreciation for Excellency in work.
- Received Service & Commitment Award from TCS.
- Developed re-usable components for the project.
- Received Start of Business Award from Accenture for Q1,FY24.